because this day is something very
special to me because it's the day that
I decided to stop walking this journey
alone I decided to walk it now with
every single one of you guys accompanied
by the people that trust in me learn
from me and succeed with me and after
thinking for a long time I realized what
I wanted to do I realized what I wanted
to do in terms of celebration for the
11-11 Oney year anniversary and for this
new challenge and that is so it all
started in 2018 when I was 18 years old
and I was working two jobs I was working
at Dunkin Donuts and I was also working
at the fair I was probably making in
total anywhere from 8 to $10 an hour but
I was working 60 70 hour weeks giving it
100% And I really wasn't sure what was
going to be of my life but however what
I did know that was clear is that I
didn't want to do this for the rest of
my life after doing the same routine for
a little over a year and a half I had
probably saved up a total of 20 to
$225,000 and I decided to do something
different I've always been very
ambitious I've always wanted to try
something different and be someone big
because I just didn't see myself being
an employee every single day of my life
for the rest of my life I just didn't
see myself living that life so with a
lot of dignity and a lot of conviction I
decided to take the Bold step of what
nobody's willing to do that is step out
of that routine step out of what people
like to call the Matrix get out of that
routine that you literally do the same
thing every single day from the moment
you either graduate high school or you
graduate college and you get a reg 9 to
5 job and you do the same thing every
single day so I quit both my jobs and I
dropped out of college when I had just
gotten started and I didn't even tell my
parents about it because they wanted me
to get a college degree but I just
simply didn't like school I didn't see
myself going there every single day and
with a little bit of digging I got into
the world of trading I stumbled across
trading and like everybody out there I
was hoping to become a millionaire
pretty much by the same week that I had
figured it out which obviously it did
not end up turning in that and it took
me 2 years uh little over $30,000 and
thousands of hours in front of the
screen to even figure out the actual way
trading works and how to be in sync with
the market to be able to date every
single dayto day of the market and
although in many occasions I was really
reconsidering what I had gotten into but
I came to the conclusion that I was
never ever going to give up no matter
what the circumstances because I know if
other people out there are successful in
trading I know I'm going to be able to
do it as well and then just like that
one day things started to change I no
longer stopped losing money I didn't go
immediately from losing money to now
making money right away I just stopped
losing money and then another 2 3 weeks
went by and I now started becoming a
little bit profitable maybe a couple
hundred maybe a couple thousand but then
a couple months after that I got my
biggest payout for the my whole entire
career at that time which was
$228,000 which paid for a whole Year's
worth of my monthly expenses and after
trial and error from learning different
strategy on YouTube from looking at
different mentors I pretty much came up
with my own strategy after getting a lot
of stuff from one of my main mentors but
I called this strategy the set and
forget strategy and this is the strategy
that led me to make millions in the
markets and this scaled really fast
literally $10,000 days became the new
normal $50,000 days became the new
normal to the point where six figure
days was just something that was part of
my day-to-day life using the set and
forget strategy and just like that my
life had complet completely changed and
this had really become the reality of
who had I had become literally coming
from Dunkin Donuts to now making six
figures in a day and not feeling
anything life actually started to feel
like GTA I would just click a couple
buttons and I would literally get
whatever I want obviously materialistic
wise because you know money could only
buy materialistic things and I started
to get the taste of this luxury life of
this lavis lifestyle in Miami you know
buying clothes eating wherever I want
and pretty much hanging out with whoever
I want because you know the luxury and
the time and the freedom that trading
was giving me and all that was fun don't
get me wrong but having access to all
that money and all that freedom so fast
actually did damage to me because I I
got bored really really fast and it got
to the point where I was doing the same
thing over and over again but with this
lavish lifestyle again it's not a bad
thing but same way how people are in a
routine for their day-to-day life I was
in a routine with my day-to-day trading
and it got boring so I had to figure out
a new challenge something that got me up
every single day excited and it just
challenged me it made me a better person
person and it got me to force myself to
not only better myself but everybody
around me and that's when I decided to
take the responsibility to open my
strategy to the community to help other
people achieve the same results as I
have and that's when swing trading lab
was born swing trading lab was born on
1111 of 2022 so exactly one year from
this video today and in one year I have
changed thousands of lives literally
getting people from working jobs to
making them full full-time Traders
getting people that they had thousands
of dollars in depth to now paying off
their debth and living from Trading and
even meeting other successful Traders
like Jordan and becoming friends with
them all thanks to the set and forget
strategy that I had opened on 1111
literally everything in just one single
year but as I had opened the swing
training lab and I'm you know changing
lives that also got kind of boring as
crazy as that might sound because it's
just the same success story right I just
teach people the strategy they become
profitable cool like it's something that
it works you could just learn your
strategy and you're going to become
profitable it's not a secret and I got
boring so then that's why I decided to
come up with a new challenge which was
this 100 to the mill and this was
something to prove to you guys that you
only need a profitable strategy to
succeed in the market you don't need to
have access to Crazy amounts of capital
once you actually understand how to
trade a profitable strategy you're going
to be able to become successful with any
amount of money obviously if you have
larger amounts of money it's less stress
less risk if you have more amounts of
money it's more reward less rest so it's
obviously just to show you guys that all
you need is a profitable strategy to
actually make money in the markets and
the best way for me to prove that to you
is with that 100 to the mill challenge
so I you know challenge myself to turn
$100 into a million in 60 days and
obviously that didn't happen I turned
$100 into
$300,000 in 11 weeks and I basically
blew it in two weeks because obviously
what I was doing is with is a very
highrisk style of trading but the point
is that I took $100 to 300K everything
is literally documented here on my
YouTube channel there's an 11 serious
Parts here on YouTube where I literally
show you guys every single trade that I
took before during and after the results
that I took everything is documented on
my YouTube telegram Instagram Discord
everywhere and all of you guys saw that
journey and this challenge actually
excited me I wasn't bored every single
day I was just excited to just complete
this Challenge and I just wanted to
complete this challenge to show you guys
that anything is possible when it comes
to trading as long as you have the right
strategy I was very excited it just got
me hyped every single day to complete it
and get one step closer to achieving it
but the unexpected happened and I
literally blew almost 3 months worth of
work in two single weeks by some very
simple mistakes that I made and I had to
get to the bottom line of what happened
to me like why did I lead to blowing
this account and when I analyze exactly
what happened to me it's a mix of work
life balance and many other things that
factored in to why I blew the account if
you want to know exactly what happened
on why I blew the account from 100 to
300K just click this link right here it
literally explains the whole entire
process of the journey up to the point
where I blew it how I blew it and how I
bounced back and and I'm here right now
and after realizing what actually
happened to me I realized that I needed
time for me so that's why I entered a
dark mode and here I decided to
disconnect myself from all social media
platforms just anybody have access to me
I literally went to a private island in
the middle of the Virgin Islands rented
a huge Villa just me and three of my
friends to just spend time by myself and
just recharge myself as a person so I
can be able to come back even stronger
with this new challenge that I'm setting
myself to do because as I'm entering the
dark mode I'm realizing that I did do
something big right I obviously turned
$100 into 300K but I almost f felt like
I had failed you guys and as I'm reading
the comments you guys are saying that
turning $100 to 300 is still a huge
success but to me it's not because I set
myself a huge goal and I I landed very
short of that and even then I still blew
the money so I technically didn't make
it so as I'm in this dark mode in the
Virgin Islands and this filla I'm
realizing wait it's about to be a
oneyear celebration of when I decided to
open my doors to my strategy and change
Traders lives forever and I'm looking
looking through my Discord I'm looking
through my testimonial and I realize I'm
like what bro I have literally changed
thousands of Traders lives in the matter
of one single year so about to be a
one-ear celebration what can I do to
make this even bigger than what I have
already done it to walk it now with
every single one of you guys accompanied
by the people that trust in me learn
from me and succeed with me and after
thinking for a long time I realized what
I wanted to do I realized what I wanted
to do in terms of Celebration for the
1111 oneye anniversary and for this new
challenge and that is where the 1111
challenge is born and this combines Best
of Both Worlds it combines the 1111 of
when I started teaching to students and
it also is going to combine the 100 to
the maale challenge I'm going to combine
both of them and that's why I'm going to
call it the 1111 Challenge and what this
is going to consist about it is a new
account that I'm going to start
with, $11 as a starting balance so now
you may ask yourself what is my goal
with these
$1,111 is it to take it to $25 million
in 30 days and the answer is no my goal
is to scale it as high as I can that's
it might sound a little boring but it's
the reality of the situation I am not
going to have a Target I am not going to
have a hard limit I am not going to have
any pressure I'm not going to put all of
this pressure on me that I already have
the 11-11 challenge is to show you guys
the importance of working with a purpose
11-11 means something so much to me
because it's when I decided to open the
doors to students and change your lives
forever so I'm going to start a new
account with the 11-11 number and the
goal is to scale it as high as I can and
just take my withdrawals as the way goes
but no time limit no hard goal no
pressure nothing and this is because the
100 to the mail had no purpose I was
just trying to take a very low amount of
money to a very high amount of money so
me waking up every single day and doing
it it was just to show you guys that
it's possible but there wasn't a
reasoning behind that number now I have
a reason every single day to wake up
because at 11-11 means something to me
so if you want to take a challenge on
with yourself now deposit an amount that
means something to you whether it's your
birthday that day you decided to start
trading have a purpose behind the
challenge don't just do it for the money
cuz I can guarantee you once you have
the profitable skill set the money will
come alone so this challenge is going to
consist of no time limit no hard goal
and no pressure but it's only going to
consist of one simple rule and that
simple rule is double the transparency
that I had in the last challenge in the
last challenge I don't know how many of
you guys scaled your accounts as well as
I did because I was putting literally
every single one of my trades out there
but in this this challenge I'm going to
be even more transparent and what do I
mean by that and that is by in my free
telegram that I have in the link in the
description below I am literally going
to send every single trade that I take
the Only Rule is that I cannot take a
trade that I don't send in the telegram
and that is me being fully transparent
and showing you guys how we're going to
scale our accounts together so every
single trade that I take in this account
I'm going to send to you guys first now
I'm not going to send a signal I don't
need to have the pressure of sending a
signal I'm going to send a trade bias so
I'm going to send an area of Interest
where I would like to have my stop- loss
and where I would like to have my
takeprofit but I'm not going to send the
exact second that I enter the exact
entry point my exact stop loss and my my
exact take profit I can't spoon feed
this either I'm going to make it as
simple and as effective as possible
without putting that much pressure on me
because again my goal is to just scale
this account as high as I can so if
there's a week or two that I don't want
to trade cool I don't have to trade that
account I'm going to still trade my
other accounts but this one is just a
side account that I'm scaling on its own
because again it means something to me
so I want to make sure I take my time
with it and I don't over pressure myself
on it so every single trade that I'm
going to take on that account I'm going
to put in the telegram and I'm going to
give you guys the bias the idea oh I'm
predicting that EUR USD and tonight's
London session if we get this I'm EXP
expecting this and then you guys will
see it play out time and time again
because that's simply what we do with
the set and forget strategy and I don't
have to put even this type of pressure
on me but I feel like my mission isn't
complete I feel like the last challenge
that I did I didn't get the job done yes
I did something huge I'll accept it I'll
take it but the job isn't done so now
I'm going to finish the job whether it
takes me 6 months whether it takes me a
year however long it takes you guys are
going to see it here on YouTube every
single week I'm going to post a you
YouTube video of the challenge you guys
are going to see it daily on my
Instagram stories you guys are going to
see the trades on my telegram everything
I don't need to do this type of
challenge but I'm doing it because I
know you guys liked it I changed
thousands of lives out there by taking
the same trades I did and to show you
guys that it's possible to become
successful from Trading all you need is
a profitable strategy and that is it you
can figure out the money other ways
whether it's by funding or just scaling
a small account and this 11-11 challenge
I feel it's the most Fair to all of us
it means something to me because it's
the one year anniversary of this day I
decided to open to my students and it's
a much better version of The 100 to the
mill challenge just something with less
rules more freedom and less pressure on
me so we're going to start this
challenge literally this Sunday which is
going to be 11:12 which one day after
the 11-11 anniversary and let the
challenge begin I appreciate you guys
watching this video all the way to the
end make sure you guys join the free
Telegram if you guys want to follow all
of the trades make sure you guys hit the
Subscribe button so you guys can see the
Journey of the account grow and if you
want to become a student where I
actually show you every single entry
point where I enter on a trade you enter
on a weekly call with me and you see how
my students are making anywhere from
$1,000 to $1,500 a week as a beginner
set foret Trader just hit the link in
the description below I have a video
there that explains more exactly on what
set and forget is but with that being
said let this 1111 challenge begin I'm
extremely excited and all I can say is
that we're going to make history once
again thank you guys